# LAKSHMI MADHURIMA KUCHIBHOTLA

## **CONTACT**



Coventry, United Kingdom CV3
5NF



07798989535



Madhurima5454@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

- Team management
- Client relations
- Energetic work attitude
- Professional and friendly
- Attentive and helpful
- Software and system training
- Desktop support
- Microsoft Office
- Computer software and system knowledge

Knowledgeable customer service management professional successful at improving team productivity, reducing escalated calls and increasing customer satisfaction scores.

Flexible Customer Service professional with 2 years of success in resolving customer concerns and enquiries. Skilled at accurately documenting call details, preparing reports and arranging service. A supportive team player, well-versed in providing helpful answers on multiple platforms to retain clients.

Collating customer feedbacks for improving the system and discussing with team for the improvement in quality of service.

## **EXPERIENCE**

February 2020 to December 2020

Customer Service Assistant Cakebox, Preston, Lancashire

- Provided friendly and attentive service by promptly responding to customer enquiries and following up on order requests.
- Helped customers select products according to individual requirements and preferences.
- Dealt with customer complaints calmly and professionally, providing appropriate solutions for continued customer satisfaction.
- Answered customer enquiries in a professional and polite manner, often going the extra mile to provide an enjoyable customer experience.
- Kept store displays looking presentable, clean and appealing by conducting [Timeframe] visual merchandising tasks.
- Worked as a team member, performing cashier duties, product assistance and cleaning.
- Efficiently processed cash and card payments during busy shopping periods using tills or [Software].

October 2019 to January 2020

Customer Service Assistant Fine fix 4 u, Preston, Lancashire

- Performed store opening duties, including counting cash drawers and checking all equipment for proper functioning.
- Efficiently processed cash and card payments during busy shopping periods using tills or software.
- Helped customers select products according to individual requirements and preferences.

July 2017 to June 2019

IT Help Desk Advisor RG2IT private limited, Hyderabad, India

- Maintained excellent team relationships by helping individuals with complex customer issues, complaints, computer malfunctions and questions.
- Provided timely and effective solutions based on information provided by customers.
- Kept up-to-date on the latest product, company, software and

system changes to stay knowledgeable for end-users.

- Provided solutions to operations issues for users of system and sofrware, working closely via phone, email, live chat and web teleconference with end users.
- Efficiently performed troubleshooting through diagnostic techniques and pertinent questions.

# **EDUCATION**

2021

Master of Science Information technology University of Central Lancashire, Preston, LAN

2017

Bachelor of Science Electronic and communication engineering K L University , Vijayawada